
const quizArray = [
  
          {
            question: "1.)Which game engine is widely used in the development of PC games, known for its versatility and popularity?",
            options: ["1.Frostbite", "2.Unreal Engine", "3.Unity", "4.CryEngine"],
            correct:"2.Unreal Engine",
          },
          {
            question: "2.)What does FPS stand for in the context of PC gaming?",
            options: ["1.Frames Per Second", "2.First-Person Shooter", "3.Full-Page Scrolling", "4.Free-to-Play Strategy"],
            correct:"1.Frames Per Second",
          },
          {
            question: "3.)What year was the first commercially successful PC game, 'Microsoft Flight Simulator,' released?",
            options: ["1.1982", "2.1995", "3.2004", "4.2010"],
            correct:"1.1982",
          },
          {
            question: "4.)Which PC game is considered the best-selling video game of all time?",
            options: ["1.Minecraft", "2.Grand Theft Auto V", "3.The Sims", "4.PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds"],
            correct:"1.Minecraft",
          },
          {
            question: "5.)Which popular PC gaming platform was developed by Valve Corporation?",
            options: ["1.Origin", "2.Steam", "3.Epic Games Store", "4.GOG"],
            correct:"2.Steam",
          },
          {
            question: "6.)Which game holds the record for the most concurrent players on Steam?",
            options: ["1.Dota 2", "2.PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds (PUBG)", "3.Counter-Strike: Global Offensive", "4.Grand Theft Auto V"],
            correct:"2.PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds (PUBG)",
          },
          {
            question: "7.)Which game introduced the concept of 'perma-death,' where the player's character permanently dies and cannot be revived?",
            options: ["1.Diablo III", "2.Dark Souls", "3.World of Warcraft", "4.The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim"],
            correct:"2.Dark Souls",
          },
          {
            question: "8.)Which PC game holds the record for the most sales in its first 24 hours after release?",
            options: ["1.World of Warcraft: Shadowlands", "2.The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim", "3.Cyberpunk 2077", "4.Red Dead Redemption 2"],
            correct:"3.Cyberpunk 2077",
          },
          {
            question: "9.)Which game franchise is known for its massive open-world environments and modding community?",
            options: ["1.Fallout", "2.The Witcher", "3.Grand Theft Auto", "4.Assassin's Creed"],
            correct:"3.Grand Theft Auto",
          },
          {
            question: "10.)What is the name of the protagonist in the 'Portal' series?",
            options: ["1.Alex Mercer", "2.Chell", "3.Gordon Freeman", "4.Lara Croft"],
            correct:"2.Chell",
          },
];